SHUBHAM GUPTA

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER (MERN) Shahganj, Jaunpur, 223102

J 9559364730 ■ shubhgupta955936@gmail.com in linkedin.com/in/shubham-gupta-2273b21aa/ 🕥 github.com/shubhamgupta100/ 🐧 hackerrank.com/shubhgupta100/ 🦝 Portfolio

About

Final year student, currently pursuing B.Tech from B.I.E.T Jhansi. I have a prior and relevant work experience in web development and have proficient in working with framework including next.js and express.js. I enjoy solving challenging problem and have worked with a good number of successful development teams.

Education

Bundelkhand Institute Of Engineering and Technology

Jul. 2018 – Jun 2022

Bachelor of Technology in Information Technology

Jhansi, U.P

Experience

Real11 Jan 2022 - Present

Software Developer Intern

- Real11 is a fantasy sports platform with 25lakh+ user
- My role is here to create api using node; and for storing data MySQL and MongoDB is being used.

MakeOurApp Jun 2021 - Aug 2021

Software Developer Intern

- During the internship period me along with team worked on a making a web application, which aim to deal with PDF file like we do in Adobe acrobat reader.
- I used MERN stack to develop the application and used next.js as a framework for react.js.

Legalshala Dec 2020 - Feb 2021

Front End Developer Intern

- During the internship period, me along with the team worked on the online communit platform www.legalshala.com
- I used frontend frameworks for the development and scratch cloning of the web pages using HTML, CSS, JS and Bootstrap and integrating in ejs templates...
- At the same time, I also made several campaign web pages on the material library.

Projects

Jan 2021 Ecommerce $\mid MERN$

- This web app is simply developed by using React .js, and Nodejs and MongoDB cloud database is used.
- In this project there are multiple components some of the m are showing product 's list, adding a review by a user and updating that review and placing an order via cart, payment integration is also done.
- Also, it has a admin panel ,admin can update order status and can add new product or update the no of stocks left. Live Project Link – https://mern-ecommerce-by-shubham.herokuapp.com/

Employee Management System | Node.js , Express.js

Nov 2020

- This web app is simply developed by using node.js, express.js and MongoDB is used used for storing data and I have used bootstrap for UI.
- This is a mini project, I have used passport is library for authentication purpose and It has funtionality of adding employee detail, multer is used for upload a file.

Live Project Link – https://ems-by-shubham.herokuapp.com/

Technical Skills

Programming: C++, Data Structure

Web Technology: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Typescript, Bootstrap, API's, DOM, React.js, Redux, Hook, Node.js,

Express.is

Database: MongoDB, MySQL

Certification

Full Stack Web Development (MERN): Coding Ninjas

Basic Programming in C++: Udemy